# **Robert Tarkenton**

#### Web Developer

Avon Lake, OH 44012 robert.tarkenton@gmail.com 440-541-6544

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/robert-tarkenton/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/robert-tarkenton/</a>
Portfolio: <a href="https://danger-academy.github.io/Portfolio/">https://danger-academy.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

Full Stack Web Developer (MERN, MySQL, variety of ORM's) with an extensive background as a manager and leader across multiple industries. Experienced team-builder and communicator. Combines military self-discipline with customer focus and a team-first attitude.

### **Work Experience**

#### **Store Manager**

GNC - General Nutrition Centers Westlake, OH December 2017 to Present

Managing specialty retail locations, providing solutions to customers with a wide array of needs and goals. Acting as primary sales driver on the floor, while also controlling inventory, scheduling the staff, addressing in-store marketing and promotions, and ensuring ongoing training. Responsible for recruiting, interviewing and hiring as needed. Consistently meets and exceeds standards for sales and profitability, as well as customer loyalty and satisfaction.

#### **Workforce Manager**

WSECU - Contact Center Olympia, WA May 2014 to June 2016

Oversaw staffing and scheduling for call center with 60+ staff. Responsible for collaborating with data analyst on forecasting, leadership team on policy development and implementation, and HR department on hiring and training. Direct communication with a diverse workforce regarding rotating schedules, vacation, and PTO in compliance with local, state, and federal laws and regulations.

(Left in order to relocate to Ohio, to raise our daughter near family.)

#### **Store Manager**

Starbucks Coffee San Diego, CA October 2010 to April 2014

Oversaw all store activities, customer, community and vendor relations, staff scheduling and training, inventory control, and implementation of in-store marketing and promotions. Maintained low staff turnover, high customer satisfaction ratings, and double-digit year-to-year increases in sales.

#### General/Regional Manager

Capriotti's Sandwich Shops Las Vegas, NV 2001 to 2010

- Assistant Manager 2001-2003
- Store Manager 2003-2004
- General Manager 2004-2010

Oversaw operations of 4 locations, including staffing and scheduling, inventory control, customer/vendor/community relations, P&L. Developed and implemented modern procedures for loss prevention, workforce planning, and forecasting, as well as marketing campaigns and promotions.

#### Owner/Operator

Prole Creative Las Vegas, NV 1998 to 2010

Freelance graphic/web designer. Clientele consisted mainly of local bands and artists, with some small businesses.

#### IT Department/ Help Desk/ Web Design First National Bank of Marin

Las Vegas, NV 1998 to 2001

Responsible for building out and implementing proprietary knowledge base for use in ticketing and troubleshooting. Assisted employees with tech issues over the phone and in person, as required. Built, rebuilt, installed and repaired hardware and peripherals. Installed and modified OS and software, and educated staff on use. Developed and maintained front end/customer facing website (html, css, JavaScript/Flash) in coordination with backend/db developers. Developed and maintained UI for company intranet.

#### **Education**

Case Western Reserve University
Full Stack Web Development Coding Bootcamp
Oct 2018 - April 2019

Wyoming Valley West High School Plymouth, PA Graduated 1993

# **Additional Skills**

MERN Stack - MySQL - Visual Studio Code - Git Experience in Project Management

# **Military Service**

**Branch: US Army** 

Corporal/ E-4

June 1993 to June 1997

Infantry/Mortars. Multiple overseas deployments.

# **Certifications/Licenses**

# **Workforce Management**

October 2015 to Present

Certified Workforce Manager (Call Center), through Injixo

# **Additional Information**

My years of experience as a leader in a variety of environments allows me to quickly and easily bring the following qualities to any position:

- Integrity and accountability
- Communication (clear, professional, compassionate)
- Adaptability.
- A positive and welcoming environment for customers and coworkers alike.

Professional references available upon request.